(Amy:)You're not answering the question.
(Amy:)- Do you love him?
- Yes, sure, of course I love him.
- It doesn't sound like it.
- Well, I do.
- Do you tell him that?
- No, he'd just take it the wrong way.
- What does that mean?
- It means he is special...
(Penny:)...and smart, and nice, and...
- Are you gonna break up with him?
- No. Maybe, I don't know.
(Bernadette:)I had no idea you were unhappy.
(Penny:)That's the thing, I'm not.
I'm not unhappy at all.
I don't know, I've been in love before
but it felt different.
(Penny:)But maybe this is a new,
better, boring kind of love.
(Penny:)Do you ever feel
that way about Howard?
(Bernadette:)That's not really a fair comparison.
(Bernadette:)I'm basically married
to a sexy Buzz Lightyear.
(Penny:)Amy, you?
Can't help you.
Whenever I'm around Sheldon...
...I feels like my loins are on fire.
(Amy:)In the good way,
not the urinary tract infection way.